Armin, I'm glad I could be
a good person to you.
You've won your bet.
But...
This is where my bet begins!
We have identified a person of interest
who may be the Female Titan.
Her name is...
Annie...
Mercy
Raid on Stohess District (2)
Several Days Earlier
They're late...
Erwin and his men are keeping me waiting.
The MP escorts will come here before they do.
He's probably constipated
and having a rough day.
You're talking a lot today, Captain.
Don't be stupid.
I always talk a lot.
I'm sorry.
Back then, if I hadn't made the wrong choice...
This never would've happened.
I told you...
No one ever knows how things will turn out.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all, sir.
You guys!
U-Um...
We have identified a person of interest
who may be the Female Titan.
This time, we won't let her escape.
The operation will be in two days.
It will take place in Stohess District,
on our way to the capital.
This is our first and last chance.
Once we pass that point, Eren will
be remanded to the capital.
Our pursuit of those who seek to destroy the walls
will become fraught with difficulty.
Ultimately, humanity stands to go extinct.
We will stake everything on this plan.
Here it is.
When we pass through Stohess,
Eren will act as a decoy,
and lead the target into
this underground tunnel.
If we can get her to the lowest level,
given the tunnel's size and structural integrity,
even if the target transforms,
we can immobilize her.
But if she transforms before then...
Eren, we'll need your help.
Yes, sir.
As for the target...
Are we sure she is in Stohess?
Yes, our target is a member
of the Military Police.
The Military Police?
It was Armin who arrived at that conclusion.
He believes the target also
killed the two captured Titans.
She may be a former trainee from
the 104th, the same as you.
W-Wait a second... The 104th?
The name of the girl we believe to
be the person of interest is...
Hey, wait...
Annie Leonhart.
C-Crap...
Damn it... That ring!
She knew I was bluffing from the start.
She knew we would ambush her.
We must have had another way!
Save it for later.
What do we need to do right now?
For now, let's meet up with
Squad 3 and get above ground.
We'll follow plan B.
We fight Annie... The Female Titan!
Eren transforms as planned,
and assists in her capture!
You'll do it, right?
Yeah!
Hey!
There's Squad 3!
Did the first capture attempt fail?
It did!
Switch to plan B!
She stomped right through the ground?!
We have to help them!
Eren...
Get back!
Hey, Mikasa...
The Female Titan's willing to let Eren die?
She made a bet...
When she created that hole,
she bet that Eren wouldn't die.
It's crazy, but it also means
she'll be tough to beat!
To take Eren, Annie's willing
to assume any risk!
What should we do?
Our exit is gone.
Even if we use our 3D Maneuver
Gear to make a quick exit,
she'll be right there waiting for us.
But if we...
If we stay here, who knows when she'll crush us?
I'll do something!
Like when I blocked that cannon shell...
Come this way!
Wait!
Let's go...
Stay close!
Not again!
No...
Now, of all times...
It hurts!
You can't transform without
a specific goal, right?
Picture it in your mind again... Clearly!
I am!
But...
Don't tell me...
You still have reservations about fighting Annie.
Eren?
After everything you've seen,
do you still think it might be all a mistake
that Annie is the Female Titan?
What did you just see?
She's the one who killed our fellow soldiers.
How can you still think that?
Shut up!
I'm trying, aren't I?!
Annie's the Female Titan?
Why?
Why do you think that, Armin?
From the start, the Female Titan
knew what you looked like.
And she reacted to your
nickname, "suicidal bastard,"
which only the 104th trainees would know.
And the biggest reason
is that I believe Annie killed the
test subjects, Sawney and Bean.
How can you tell?
Only someone very skilled could have done it.
And they'd have used their own Maneuver
Gear, which they're accustomed to.
Yeah, wasn't that why they
inspected our Maneuver Gear?
But they didn't find anything on Annie...
Annie brought Marco's Maneuver
Gear to the inspection.
That's why she managed
to avoid getting caught.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
What does Marco have to do with this?
I don't know.
Are you sure it was his?
Yes, I know what I—
Hey, kid.
We get it.
Do you have any other evidence?
No, I don't.
I think Annie's face resembles the Female Titan's.
Huh?
What are you talking about?!
That isn't evidence—
So, you have no proof,
but you'll do it anyway.
You have no proof?
What?
Then why do it?
What if it isn't her?
Then we'll know she's innocent. That's all.
And then I'll feel bad for Annie.
However, if we don't do something,
you'll end up being sacrificed
to the people in the capital!
You're crazy to think Annie's a Titan.
Eren, now that you know we suspect her,
isn't it ringing any bells?
You fought the Female Titan.
Didn't anything remind you of
Annie's distinctive combat style?
You do know, don't you?
You know Annie is the Female Titan.
Then we should fight her, shouldn't we?
Or do you have certain feelings
for her? Is that what's stopping you?
Huh?
I have a plan!
Mikasa and I will exit at the same time,
using the original entrance and that opening.
Annie will attack one of us.
Use that opportunity to get
out from the other exit!
Wait!
Then one of you will die!
If we stay here, we all die, anyway!
Mikasa, take your position!
Right.
I'll take the front.
Mikasa!
Armin!
How?
How can you fight her?
How?!
We don't have a choice.
The world is cruel.
Information We Can Share So Far:
Wall Sina (1)
Wall Sina encloses the capital and about 200,000 people.
Residency requires special permission and is technically
restricted to the royal family and their relatives.
Information We Can Share So Far:
Wall Sina (2)
One may also earn residency rights through meritorious
service in the Garrison or Military Police, which is
considered the sole means for the poor to gain safe refuge.
Eren!
Annie, I won't let you have Eren!
Eren...
I'll get you out!
Open your eyes...
Don't let the Female Titan escape!
Don't let her get out!
What happened?
Escort team, we don't need you here!
Go see what's happening!
Roger!
Something's off...
That explosion I heard...
Nile...
Deploy all of your troops.
We should assume a Titan has appeared.
Wh-What?!
This is Wall Sina...
There's no way a Titan could be here!
Wait! Don't move, Jaeger!
I'm done with this disguise!
Never call me by that name again, moron!
Commander, I'm going, too.
Get your equipment from Squad 4.
Roger!
It's good to see that someone
has the balls to go,
but don't forget to do your
damnedest to stay alive.
Yes, sir.
Erwin, what is this?
Commander, here!
Good work.
Hey, Erwin!
Anyone who can move, follow me!
We'll rendezvous with the capture teams.
Erwin, wait.
What you're doing is clearly
treason against the crown!
Nile, I'm starting to wonder if your brains don't
even live up to that sorry excuse of a beard.
Seems to me that you don't even
have a clue what's going on.
Remove your equipment, Erwin!
A Titan! A Titan's here!
What's it doing here?
Run!
Hey, isn't that a Titan?
Yeah... But how?
Out of the way!
Damn those slackers!
I could've been one of them.
What the hell happened?
Damn it!
Don't attempt to kill it.
Just try to slow it down!
It's no use... It knows how
Maneuver Gear works!
I'm not going to make
this easy on you!
Eren!
Answer me! Eren!
Hey! What are you doing?
Jean!
Eren's trapped!
The plan was for him to become a Titan!
He couldn't...
I think the fact that it's Annie is stopping him.
Annie?
Anyway, we have to save him!
Jean, help me!
He couldn't transform?
Eren, what the hell is wrong with you?!
Didn't I once tell you that
I'm counting on you?
We have to entrust the world,
humanity, and our lives to you,
and this is how you repay us?
Marco... Marco...
Damn it!
Eren...
It's no use...
We have to do something about her first!
Eren, I said this once to Jean...
Someone who can't sacrifice anything
can never change anything...
That to defeat monsters, you have to be
willing to throw aside your humanity.
Annie is certainly capable of doing that...
although I don't know what her reasons are.
But whoever can do it will win!
Annie!
If you can't kill me this time,
you can't make the same bullshit excuse
that your bet's just beginning anymore!
Armin, this way!
Roger!
It's coming...
It's coming.
Squad Leader...
You have a crazy look in your eyes.
Okay!
I thought there'd be no need
for a plan C, but nope...
That's Commander Erwin for you, I guess.
Now, then...
Be a good girl.
Stay put.
Here, you're too far in to get Titans
to devour you like before.
But don't worry...
I'll be the one devouring you instead.
I'll devour all the information
that we can drag out of you.
She broke free?
We needed more traps!
Don't let her escape! Follow her!
Someone who can't sacrifice anything
can never change anything!
I know that...
That's why I failed.
I clung to my companions and
my ties to them, and I failed.
Remember...
I'll wipe you out...
No...
I'll kill you!
There's no time to figure out
if this is the right thing to do!
Just move...
Don't try to keep your hands clean!
That's right...
Mikasa!
The world is cruel!
Now what?
Eren!
Eren...
"I will eradicate Titans from this world."
The same fury that led Eren to make
that vow on that fateful day
now spurs him on...
to destroy the entire world.
The Wall
Raid on Stohess District (3)